A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of Civilian Defense, 1940-1945.
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Correspondence, 1942-1945., Extent: 10.15 cubic feet (29 boxes). (Box 1-29)
  - Correspondence, 1943-1945.
    - Leonard, Donald S., Capt. (Michigan Office of Civilian Defense, 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Lewis, Rosa B. (Powhatan County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Lib-Liv - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Lichtman, A. E. (Theater Manager), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Limbrick, A. C. (Spotsylvania County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Lindsey, C. H. (Northumberland County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Linzel, Frank A., Mrs. (U.S. Civilian War Services), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Litex Products Company, 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Lob-Lyz - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Locher, Charles H., Mrs. (Rockbridge County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Loeb, Charles S. (Litex Products Company), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Loewner, Laurence L. (Harrisonburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Long, Paul B. (West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Long, Raymond V. (State Planning Board), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Loughborough, R. M. (Fairfax County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Luebert, C. H. (Virginia State Salvage Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Lowe, William H. (Lancaster County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Lowry, Lolita (Elizabeth City County), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Mab-May - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Mac - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - MacMillan, Theresa (Dept. of Public Welfare), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Mahaffey, S. J. (Henrico County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Marchant, A. B. (Middlesex County), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Markey, D. John, Col. (Camp Pickett), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Marks, Mary V., 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Marshall, Richard M. (Norfolk CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Martin, Fred P. (Wythe County CDC - Civilain Mobilization), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Martin, John B. (U.S. Office of Civilian Defense), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Martin, R. W. (North Carolina Council of Defense), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Martin, T. I. (Culpeper County CDC - Civilian Mobilization), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Marye, Burton (State Highway Dept.), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Mason, C. G. (Page County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Mason, C. Y. (Waynesboro CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Massey, C. C. (Henrico County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Martin, Mary I. (State Dept. of Health), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Matthews, Walter W. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - McA-McW - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - McCarthy, Claire (Richmond CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - McCall, H. R., Capt. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - McCleary, Robert W. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - McClellan, G. E. (E. I. Dupont de Nemours and Co.), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - McCloskey, S. T., Lt. Col. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - McDearmon, C. S. (Appomattox County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - McElroy, Robert M., Dr. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - McGuire, Walter P. (Southside Virginia News), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - McGuffin, I. J. (Halifax County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - McIntyre, W. T. (Staunton CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - McMillan, R. L. (North Carolina Civilian Defense Council), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - McNamee, Frank A., Col. (U.S. Office of Civilian Defense), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - McRee, Fergus (Richmond Postmaster), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Mea-Mey - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Memoranda, 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Messer, Richard I., Maj. (State Dept. of Health - Sanitary Engineering), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Meyer, Edwin O. (Virginia Press Association), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Mic-Mit - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Michael, R. D. (Blacksburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Miller, G. Tyler (Warren County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Miller, H. A., Jr. (Petersurg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Miller, Macon P. (Radford CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Minter, W. M. (Mathews County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Moa-Mox - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Modlin, George M. (University of Richmond), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Moffett, C. K. (The Plains Warning District), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Moffett, Miledge, Dr. (Radford CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Monticello Hotel, 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Moody, Warren (State Gas Consultant), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Moomaw, Edward C., Lt. (Naval Intelligence Service), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Moore, C. E. (Conserve Critical Resources), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Moore, Frances I. (State Nutrition Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Moore, Stuart (Lexington CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Morris, Bonney M. (Richmond County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Morris, Goldie (Harrisonburg-Rockingham CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Morris, O. M. (Pound CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Morton, R. Page (Charlotte County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Moses, C. T. (Appomattox County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Mottley, Robert C., Lt. Col. (Chemical Officer), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Moxom, W. J. (United States Weather Bureau), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Muc-Myr - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Mullen, C. S. (State Dept. of Highways), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Murphy, William A. (Federal Bureau of Investigation), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Murphy, W. Tayloe (State Treasurer/Virginia War Fund), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Murray, Douglas, Mrs. (Fairfax County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Murray, J. C. (Montgomery County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Myers, P. G. (Harrisonburg-Rockingham CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Myers, William M., Col. (Virginia State-wide Safety Conference), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Nab-New - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Nathan, Harold (Federal Bureau of Investigation), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Neal, Mills F., Col. (State Selective Service System), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Neasmith, John I. (Federal Security Agency) 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Nelson, O. K. (North Tazewell CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Nettleton, Charles (Covington CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Neugent, Mary W. (State Nutrition Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Newman, Houston H. (Shenandoah County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Nia-Nys - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Nolan, E. J. (Merck and Company), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Nolan, William J., Capt. (Third Service Command - Virginia District), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Nunn, J. R., Maj. (Dept. of State Police), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Nutter, Josephine (Fairfax County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - O - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Oberfell, C. R. (Lynchburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Ober, Douglas (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Odom, Woodrow (Isle of Wight CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Older, Isabel S. (Office of the U.S. Secretary of War), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Oliver, L. T. (Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Olsen, E. S. (Martinsville CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Orton, Vernon A. (Accomac County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Osborn, James M. (Connecticut War Council), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Owens, Arthur S. (Portsmouth CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Owen, W. Wycliffe, Dr. (Gas Specialist), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Pac-Pey - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Padgett, Bernard J. (Alexandria CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - Page, R. D. (Richmond County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - Page, W. Thomas (King George County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - Parcell Claude T. (Fredericksburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Parker, Henry G. (Dept. of Public Welfare - Norfolk), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Parker, W. L. (Stephens City CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - Parrish, B. S., Maj. (Virginia Protective Service), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Patterson, Myrtle (Lynchburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 58)
    - Patton, James J., Rev. (Waynesboro CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 24, Folder 59)
    - Pea-Pey - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Peach, J. M., Chief (Dept. of Public Safety - Norfolk), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Pederson, F. C. (Forest Fire Fighters Service), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Peebles, John K., Jr. (Air Raid Shelter Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Pierce, C. T., Mrs. (Lancaster County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Pendleton, Nat W. (State Technical Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania Hotel, 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Pfa-Ply - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Phillips, James W. (State Dept. of Public Welfare), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Phillips, R. B., Dr. (Caroline County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Pierce, William E., Lt. Col. (U.S. Office of Civilian Defense - Harrisburg Office), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Poa-Poy - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Pobst, H. Claude (Buchanan County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Poff, J. H. (Floyd County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Poindexter, Maggie (Harrisonburg and Rockingham County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Poole, J. H. (Bluefield CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Potter, C. J., Dr. (U.S. Dept. of the Interior - Solid Fuels), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Powell, George T. (Staunton CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Powell, R. H. (Franklin CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Powers, D. A. (York County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Pra-Pyr - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Preston, T. W., Hon. (Bristol CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Program Managers - Radio Stations, 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Pulley, Junius W. (Southampton County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Purcell, Edward (Conserve Critical Resources), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Purchase and Printing, Dept. of, 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Q, 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Raa-Ray - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Radcliffe, Sarah, RN (State Health Dept.), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Radford, Duval (Bedford County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Railway Express Agency, 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Ransford, John (Bath County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Rea-Rho - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Reckford, Milton A., Maj. Gen. (Third Service Command), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Reed, Mary Frances (VPI - Nursery Schools), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Reninger, Henry A., Col. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943 Jan-July. (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Reninger, Henry A., Col. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943 Aug-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Reninger, Henry A., Col. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1944. (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Renkin, Harold I. (Pocahontas CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Revell, W. Grant (Conserve Critical Resources Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Rhein, E. B. (Westmoreland County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Ria-Riz - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Rice, J. Linwood (Virginia War Fund), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Rice, P. A. (State Technical Committee/RF and P Railroad), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Rider, Cowl (Richmond Information Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Riffe, C. S. (Burkevill CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Riggin, I. C., Dr. (State Health Dept.), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Risney, C. J., Capt. (Richmond Air Base), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Ritter, Harry C. (War Protection Board), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Roa-Roy - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Roane, John R. (Westmoreland County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Roanoke Hotel, 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Robb, R. G., Dr. (College of William and Mary - Chemistry Dept.), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Robbins Company, 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Robertson, A. Stuart (Orange County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Robinson, J. W. (Louisa County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Rodgers, R. L. (Rileyville CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Roecker, F. C. (Richmond Army Service Forces Depot), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Ross, Charles J. (Madison County), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Roudabush, R. E. (Shenandoah County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Rowan, James H. (Halifax County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Rowe, F. A. (Johns-Manville Products Corp.), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Rua-Ryn - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Russell, J. Alvin, Rev. (Brunswick County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Ryder, Melvin (Civilian Front), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Ryder, W. A. (Royster Guano Company), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Saa-Sey - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Sanger, W. T., Dr. (State Nutrition Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Scarff, John H., Dr. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Schaff, C. Hart, Dr. (Office of Price Administration), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Schraffenberger, L. G. (U.S. Office of Civilian Defense - Protection Services), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Scott, Don E., Brig. Gen. (Third Service Command), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Scott, Eugene, Maj. (U.S. Office of Civilian Defense - Nat. Gas Officer), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Scott, Fontaine H. (Conserve Critical Resources Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Sellew, Roland W., Lt. Col. (Third Service Command - Pland Protection), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Sha-Shu - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Shaughnessy, Harry (Office of Price Administration - Roanoke), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Shelburne, T. P. (Office of Price Administration), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Shepherd, Fred R. (Colonial Heights CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Sib-Smy - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Simmonds, Gene (Third Civilian Defense Council), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Simmons, James W. (Prince Edward County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Sinclair, J. B., Jr. (Hampton City Hall), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Skeppstrom, T. (Proctor and Gamble Manufacturing Company), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Skinnell, J. F. (WMBG Radio Station), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Skinner, Albert M., Lt. Col. (U.S. Office of Civilian Defense), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Slocum, Sylvia (District Home Demonstration Agent), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Small, Sydney F. (Roanoke CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Smith, A. G., Jr. (V.P.I. Extension Service), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Smith, D. L. (Norfolk County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Smith, E. Armstrong (Cumberland County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Smith, J. Lawrence (Portsmouth CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Sna-Sty - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Snidow, W. S. (Christiansburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Stallard, B. H. (St. Paul CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Stanley, Thomas B. (House of Delegates), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Staples, Abram P. (State Attorney General), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Staples, E. W. (Conserve Critical Rsources Committee - Suffolk), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Starbuck, Wilson, Commander (Naval Operating Base - Norfolk), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - State Comptroller, 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - State Reports, 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Stauffer, William A. (State Emergency Welfare Services), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Steel, R. E. (Virginia Railway Association), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Stephenson, Harold (Fluvanna County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Stern, Phillip N. (State Technical Committee) 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Stewart, Clara (Essex County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Stoneburner, C. G. (Arlington County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Stuart, Charles E. (Westmoreland County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Stuart, Walter P. (Saltville CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Sub-Szo - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Sullivan, Daniel P. (Princess Anne County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Sullivan, Willard, Mrs. (Hanover County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Summergill, R. W. (United States Rubber Company), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Sunderland, A. H., Gen. (Elizabeth City County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Sutherland, H. M., Mrs. (Dickenson County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Sutton, D. N. (King William County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Sutton, James E. (Norfolk County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Symington, Francis F., Mrs. (Third Regional Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Tab-Tex - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Talley, E. M. (Floyd County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Tate, V. B. (Wise County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Taylor, George K., Jr. (Amelia County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Temple, T. Edward (Hopewell CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Templeton, Furman L. (Third Regional Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Terry, Catherine W. (Charlottesville CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Tha-Thu - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Thoma, J. Edward (Clarke County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Thomas, E. S. (State Technical Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Thomas, Lonny (Alta Vista CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Thomas, Norris L. (York County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Thomas, W. C., Capt. (Dept. of State Police), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Thomasset, R. G. (Arlington County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Thompson, Lorin, Dr. (Virginia State Committee on Child Care), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Thompson, Mary L. (Emergency War Food Preservation - V.P.I.), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Thompson, Perry A. (Stafford County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Thorson, A. W. (Dept. of the Interior - Solid Fuels), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Tib-Tow - Miscellaneous), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Tiffany, Hunton (Prince William County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Tinner, Ollie (Fairfax County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Toler, C. Henry (Office of Price Administration), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Todd, Bays M. (Grayson Councy CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Tompkins, G. S. (American Viscose Corporation), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 32a)
    - Tra-Tyu - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Trigg, Emma Gray (Office of Price Administration), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Tuck, William M. (Lt. Governor of Virginia), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Tucker, Floyd W., Jr. (Hanover County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Tucker, J. L., Rev. (Stanley CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Tuggle, H. Irvine, Mrs. (Martinsville CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Turman, Charles F., Mrs. (Accomack County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Turnbull, Graeme (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Turner, C. A., Rev. (York County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Turner, G. T. (Northampton County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Turner, Horatio W. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Turner, Lewis J. (Rappahannock County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Turner, L. R. (Southampton County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Tyler, J. Alfred (Charles City County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - U - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Updike, C. O. (Bedford County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Updike, Ira A. (Hanover County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - V - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Van Benthuysen, F. H., Mrs. (Hopewell CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Vass, I. G. (Waynesboro CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Vaughan, C. C. (Franklin CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Vaughan, Earl H. (Solid Fuels Admistration), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Vickers, Mantelle (Third Service Command), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Virginian Hotel, 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Wac-Way - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Waggaman, Ennalls, Maj. (Washingon CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Walke, I. T., Jr., Lt. Comm. (Naval Intelligence Service), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Walker, Robert B. (Fairfax County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Walker, T. C. (Gloucester County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Wales, Emory T. (King George County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Wallace, John G. (Norfolk County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Wallace, Maude E. (V.P.I. Extension Service), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Wallenborn, P. A. (Conserve Critical Resources Committee - Charlottesville), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Waller, S. Gardner, Brig. Gen. (Adjutant General of Virginia), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Walton, Clarence E. (Massachusetts Committee on Public Service), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Walton, W. A. (Prince George County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Wankle, W. B., Jr. (Dinwiddie County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Warden, J. B., Col. (U.S. Office of Civilian Defense - Industrial Protection), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - War Production Board, 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Wardwell, E. H. (Northumberland County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Ware, Edward P. (Elizabeth City County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 28, Folder 30)